How to Create a New Fashion Style
1.
Create a New Fashion Style
Click on the 2D version of the menu, then select the version of the designer.
Next, please select the clothing type.
Currently, only the t-shirt is supported, and more options will be added later.
Then, according to the style you need to choose, the style of the t-shirt is divided by the sleeve type.
At the bottom, you will see the basic measurement data of the clothing.
For how to view and adjust your measurement data, you have three different options.
The regular option will provide you with a complete list of common measurement points.
The simple option will provide you with the most common measurement point to simplify the editing process.
The user-defined option allows you to customize your own measurement list and determine the measurement data according to your needs.
You can click on the eye icon to select which clothing versions you want to create.
You can switch the version to symmetrical or left-right symmetrical.
All measurement options can be used to display all measurement data of the version.
Click on the Detailed Information button.
You can switch to display all measurement data.
to display the list of all measurement information.
Select the measurement data that needs to be selected.
After the setting is complete,
click the button to change the application.
Enter your version measurement value.
You can click the reset button next to each measurement data
to restore it to its original value.
Some measurement items will contain a total length option
used to enter the circumference of the front and back pieces.
Some measurement items also contain a pull-down option
used to select the measurement location applied to the measurement data.
You can click to display all measurement icons
to view all non-actual measurement items in each section.
Click the Create button to create clothing in the 2D and 3D windows.
You can also use the AI version generator to generate data.
The AI version generator will automatically generate measurement data
and create draft versions for you.
Click the AI version generator button in the upper right corner of the version generator.
Enter the key word to generate a picture
or directly upload a picture to generate the result.
Select the clothing type and enter your draft inspiration.
Please make sure to add as many descriptive words as possible.
If you want to emphasize certain content,
please put it in the brackets.
Currently, only the T-shape can be selected.
Later, more other styles will be introduced.
A small tip.
Please try to provide sentences that describe accurate words
and not long sentences
to produce more effective results.
Click on the Keyword suggestion to display the power key words
to help you generate key words.
Even if you use the same keyword,
the AI picture will be re-created each time.
Therefore, click on the Keyword button
to update the key words.
Keep the existing results as much as possible.
According to the addition or change of key words,
the result may be different from the existing result.
Click on the Create button at random
to add the power key words to the text prompt at random.
Click on the Create button to create a picture.
Here are the key words.
Click the Clear button to clear all content
to begin the creative process.
Click on the Upload button
to add a reference image that is in line with the following guidelines.
Use the white background and black linebacker
to ensure that the AI image has a high quality.
Ensure that the image only has the clothing image.
This process can be repeated until you get the desired result.
After creating the version, open the simulation and put the costume on the virtual model.
That's all for this video. See you in the next video.